(Bernadette:)I've been working
on this facial expression all day.
(Amy:)And I appreciate your effort...
(Amy:)...but upon contemplation,
I decided I was being selfish.
So I canceled our dinner reservations...
(Amy:)...and came up with an even better way
to celebrate Valentine's Day.
- What is that?
- By doing none of it.
(Amy:)No dinner, no romance, no gifts.
(Amy:)We stay here, order a pizza...
(Amy:)...and watch one
of your beloved Star War Trek things.
(Sheldon:)Really?
(Amy:)That's what you'd love, isn't it?
(Sheldon:)More than anything.
Well, then, that's what we're gonna do.
(Sheldon:)Well, I don't know what to say.
(Sheldon:)This is the most thoughtful gift
that anyone's ever given me.
(Sheldon:)And that's including an amazing gift
I gave myself earlier today.
(Amy:)I'm your girlfriend, that's my job.
I know gift-giving puts pressure on you
so whatever you got me, you can return.